let savollar23 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "Aborigine",
      answer: "C. eski avstraliyalik",
      options: [
        "A. sayyoh",
        "B. rassom",
        "C. eski avstraliyalik",
        "D. dengizchi"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "to ban",
      answer: "A. taqiqlamoq",
      options: [
        "A. taqiqlamoq",
        "B. raqsga tushmoq",
        "C. pishirmoq",
        "D. chizmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "cautious",
      answer: "D. ehtiyotkor",
      options: [
        "A. baxtli",
        "B. charchagan",
        "C. kuchli",
        "D. ehtiyotkor"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "to confess",
      answer: "B. tan olmoq",
      options: [
        "A. yugurmoq",
        "B. tan olmoq",
        "C. uxlamoq",
        "D. kuylamoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "cottage",
      answer: "C. qishloq uyi",
      options: [
        "A. ko'prik",
        "B. zavod",
        "C. qishloq uyi",
        "D. aeroport"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "daytime",
      answer: "A. kunduzi",
      options: [
        "A. kunduzi",
        "B. fasl",
        "C. hafta",
        "D. asr"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "desperate",
      answer: "D. ilojsiz",
      options: [
        "A. och",
        "B. boy",
        "C. dangasa",
        "D. ilojsiz"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "to fade",
      answer: "B. rangi o'chmoq",
      options: [
        "A. o'smoq",
        "B. rangi o'chmoq",
        "C. sakramoq",
        "D. uchmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "fierce",
      answer: "C. yirtqich",
      options: [
        "A. tinch",
        "B. mehribon",
        "C. yirtqich",
        "D. sekin"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "to gamble",
      answer: "A. qimor o'ynamoq",
      options: [
        "A. qimor o'ynamoq",
        "B. tozalamoq",
        "C. pishirmoq",
        "D. tikmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "lawn",
      answer: "D. maysa",
      options: [
        "A. tom",
        "B. devor",
        "C. deraza",
        "D. maysa"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "to mow",
      answer: "B. o'rmoq",
      options: [
        "A. ekmoq",
        "B. o'rmoq",
        "C. sug'ormoq",
        "D. chopmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "outlaw",
      answer: "C. qidiruvdagi shaxs",
      options: [
        "A. o'qituvchi",
        "B. novvoy",
        "C. qidiruvdagi shaxs",
        "D. shifokor"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "prospect",
      answer: "A. istiqbol",
      options: [
        "A. istiqbol",
        "B. ta'm",
        "C. hid",
        "D. ovoz"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "purse",
      answer: "D. hamyon",
      options: [
        "A. poyabzal",
        "B. shlyapa",
        "C. palto",
        "D. hamyon"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "rod",
      answer: "B. tayoq",
      options: [
        "A. stol",
        "B. tayoq",
        "C. stul",
        "D. karavot"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "seldom",
      answer: "C. kamdan-kam",
      options: [
        "A. doimo",
        "B. tez-tez",
        "C. kamdan-kam",
        "D. ba'zan"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "to shave",
      answer: "A. soqol olmoq",
      options: [
        "A. soqol olmoq",
        "B. yuvmoq",
        "C. taramoq",
        "D. cho'tkalash"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "terrified",
      answer: "D. dahshatga tushgan",
      options: [
        "A. xursand",
        "B. xafa",
        "C. jahldor",
        "D. dahshatga tushgan"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "wizard",
      answer: "B. sehrgar",
      options: [
        "A. dehqon",
        "B. sehrgar",
        "C. baliqchi",
        "D. ovchi"
      ]
    }
];

export default savollar23;